(Sheldon:)Forgot my keys.
(Howard(on phone):)Okay, great. Bye.
Our friendly neighborhood scalper
says he's running late.
(Raj:)Does he sound like a criminal?
(Howard:)What do you mean?
(Raj:)You know, did he say things like,
"Youse guys," or "Listen here, see?"
Yes. He's late because
he's on his way here from 1940.
(Raj:)I'm just saying.
We don't know who this guy is.
(Raj:)What if he wants to steal
our money or our kidneys,
or make a suit out of our skins?
(Howard:)Why would someone want to make
clothes out of your skin?
(Raj:)I don't know. Maybe 'cause
dark doesn't show the stains?
(Leonard:)Now you're making me wonder
if we should have met him
(Leonard:)at a neutral location.
(Howard:)Why do you think I told him
to come to your place?